<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no"?>
<modDesc descVersion="80">
    <author>GMNGjoy</author>
    <version>1.0.0.1</version>
    <title>
        <en>BioBaler Pro</en>
        <de>Profi BioBaler</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[A PRO version of the Anderson BioBaler with support for extra & larger bale sizes.

Both BioBaler WB-55 Pro & BioBaler WB-55 Cotton:
- Price: $99101
- Required HP: 150
- Working Width: 2.5m (adjustable with the VPW settings)

Poplar Bale sizes:
- 125cm (4000L)
- 150cm (6000L)
- 180cm (8000L)

Also included is a cotton version of the Anderson BioBaler with custom cotton bales in the standard baler bale sizes.

Cotton Bale sizes:
- 125cm (2600L)
- 150cm (3200L)
- 180cm (3800L)

All custom bales can be picked up with base game equipment like the Anderson RBM 2000.

AND... If that wasn't enough, this mod also adds in Variable Pickup Width (VPW) support, which adds a custom workMode allowing you to select from 4 different pickup widths:
- Default Pickup (default)
- Bonus Pickup (+2m)
- Extended Pickup (+4m)
- Virtual Windrower (20m)

Note: In rare cases when saving, leaving the game and coming back in with a VPW work mode selected - it will appear that the pickup area has not been adjusted correctly. To remedy this, just cycle through the work modes again to your selection, and continue on.

Each item costs $1 more than basegame, works a bit faster and has full color selection.

For license & feedback, please visit: https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS22_BioBalerPro

CHANGELOG 1.0.0.1
- Fixed bale drop animation]]>
		</en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Die PRO Version des Anderson BioBaler mit Unterstützung für zusätzliche Ballengrößen.

Sowohl für den BioBaler WB-55 Pro als auch für den BioBaler WB-55 Baumwolle gilt:
- Preis: 99101€
- Benötigte PS: 150
- Arbeitsbreite: 2,5m (Die Arbeitsbreite kann umkonfiguriert werden)

Ballengrößen für Pappeln:
- 125cm (4000L)
- 150cm (6000L)
- 180cm (8000L)

Zusätzlich ist eine Baumwoll-Version des Anderson BioBaler mit neuen Baumwoll-Ballen in den Standard Ballengrößen enthalten.

Ballengrößen für Baumwolle:
- 125cm (2600L)
- 150cm (3200L)
- 180cm (3800L)

Alle zusätzlichen Ballen können mit Geräten aus dem Basisspiel, wie dem Anderson RBM 2000, aufgehoben werden.

UND... falls das noch nicht genug war, unterstützt diese Mod auch eine Variable Arbeitsbreite, die es ermöglicht, aus vier verschiedenen Arbeitsbreiten zu wählen:
- Standard Arbeitsbreite (Standard)
- Zusätzliche Arbeitsbreite (+2m)
- Erweiterte Arbeitsbreite (+4m)
- Virtueller Schwader (20m)

Hinweis: In seltenen Fällen kann es nach dem Speichern, Verlassen und erneuten Laden des Spiels so aussehen als ob die Arbeitsbreite nicht richtig angepasst wurde. Um das Problem zu lösen, musst du nur einmal durch die Arbeitsbreiten rotieren und kannst dann die Arbeit fortführen.

Jedes Gerät kostet 1€ mehr als im Basisspiel, arbeitet etwas schneller und unterstützt die volle Farbauswahl.

Besucht für Lizenz und Feedback bitte https://github.com/GMNGjoy/FS22_BioBalerPro

CHANGELOG 1.0.0.1
- Animation zum Abladen der Ballen verbessert]]>
		</de>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_bioBalerPro.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />

	<storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/bioBalerWB55Pro.xml" />
        <storeItem xmlFilename="xml/bioBalerWB55Cotton.xml" />
    </storeItems>

    <bales>
        <!-- biomass bales -->
        <bale filename="roundbales/biomassBale125_4k.xml" />
		<bale filename="roundbales/biomassBale150_6k.xml" />
        <bale filename="roundbales/biomassBale180_8k.xml" />

        <!-- cotton bales -->
        <bale filename="roundbales/cottonRoundbale125.xml" />
        <bale filename="roundbales/cottonRoundbale150.xml" />
        <bale filename="roundbales/cottonRoundbale180.xml" />
	</bales>

    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="cottonBalerWorkMode" parent="baseGroundToolFillable" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="workMode" />
            <specialization name="combine" />
            <specialization name="cutter" />
            <specialization name="baler" />
            <specialization name="dynamicMountAttacher" />
        </type>

        <type name="cuttingBalerWorkMode" parent="cuttingBaler" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
			<specialization name="workMode" />
		</type>
    </vehicleTypes>

    <l10n filenamePrefix="languages/l10n" />
</modDesc>
